That as long as Kabir businessmen of this juice are
considering it as an enemy that there will be fog, then it should be
made in the same manner throughout 26th January keeping
social distancing in mind,
but I do
not want any farmer brother to oppose it
or put it after SIM, this is a
historical moment for our country, once a year we
celebrate Republic Day from 26th January, on this day
we got all the facilities, keeping in mind the dignity of that constitution, I would
appeal to the farmer brothers that they can
continue their protest at the place where they are protesting, they should
not insult the country by obstructing the plate like the meter, they are also citizens of the country, they should
think about the respect of this country,
so that I would like to wish all the countrymen and the
people of the area on 26th January
that we should continue
celebrating our Republic Day in this manner every year,
heartiest wishes to everyone.